haathichiti.com 2015-12-28

# Privacy Policies

## Privacy Policies For Haathichiti.com.

We recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit http://www.haathichiti.com, and how we safeguard your information. These privacy policies are applies to the site and all the products and services offered by this website.

### Personal Identification Information

We may collect personal information identification information from users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to when users visits our site or respond to a survey and in connection with other activities, services, features and resources we make available on our site. User may be asked for appropriate name, email address, phone number. We will collect Personal Identification Information from users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply Personal Identification Information.

### Non Personal Identification Information

We may collect non Personal Identification Information about users whenever they interact with our website. Non Personal Identification Information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical info about users means of connection to our site, such as the OS and internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

### Web Browse Cookies

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

### How we use collect Information

Haathichiti.com collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:

– To personalize user experience

we may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.

– To improve our Site

we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.

– To improve customer service

your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.

– To send periodic emails

the email address Users provide will only be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

### How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

### Don’t sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

### Google Adsense

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the dart cookies enables it to serve ads to user based on their visit to our site and other sites on the internet. Dart uses ‘non personally identification information’ and does not track personal information about you, such as your name, email and physical address etc. You may opt out of the use of DART cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/>.

### Compliance With Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

### Changes to the Privacy Polices

Haathichiti.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

### Your Acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
